This series is crafted for the purpose of entertainment.
All characters, behaviours, settings, and events depicted in this drama are entirely fictitious.
They are not designed to allude to any particular entity, occupation, or group of people.
Viewer discretion is advised.
[North Star Entertainment]
♫Always making that face whenever you see me♫
[7HD Channel]
[iQIYI]
♫Always making that face whenever you see me♫
♫What does that mean?♫
[Present]
♫Whatever I say upset you, but you’ll get mad if I keep quiet♫
♫I really don’t know what to do♫
♫When deep down, I really like you♫
♫But you probably don’t care♫
♫Should I just say it out loud?♫
♫Or keep it all to myself and let it be?♫
♫What should I do?♫
♫I don’t know how to tell you how I feel♫
♫I’m still confused by the way you react when I’m around♫
♫I’m still afraid. Will it be all right if I say it?♫
♫So I have to hide it inside♫
♫I don’t know what to do with these feelings♫
♫Always keep dreaming of you, night after night♫
♫What should I do? I can’t just let it go on like this♫
♫But I’m too afraid to say it, so I’ll just keep it to myself♫
Flaming Chains of Love
[Previously]
Is there anything else you have to do today?
No, I’m taking a half day off today.
Then, let’s go find something to eat.
Don’t tell me you’ve been stalking me.
You seem to know her well.
Then, I guess you also know about her Phi Jah.
Nod!
Who the hell is Jah?
What?
If you want her to love you, you should try to pamper her.
Take her out to nice places, and eat something delicious.
She’ll definitely fall for you.
You’ve split up with Jee since afternoon but why are you just home now?
If you love me, don’t ever let me down. Do you understand?
I came back this time
because I intend to never let Phrao go again.
Thank you, Phi Jah, for taking me out today.
What are you doing here?
Well, I have to go to Bangkok with Dad.
So, I won’t be able to take you out this weekend.
Huh?
You came here just to tell me that?
Mhm.
I don’t want you to wait.
Weird.
What’s weird?
You’re suddenly being nice.
You hated it when I was being mean, and now you’re complaining when I’m being nice.
I’m just who I am. Aren't you used to it yet?
I am! That’s why it feels so weird when you’re being this nice.
Look, if I finally decide to be nice to you–
it’s you who’d be in trouble.
Because you won’t be able to resist it, Silly Gremlin.
I gotta go.
Don’t forget to come to the main house to see me and Dad off.
I've changed my mind.
Just come with me now.
Go and wait in the car first.
Have a safe trip, Uncle.
Thanks a lot, Little One.
I’ll leave it in your hands here.
Please don’t worry.
Don’t try to take over all his businesses.
Yod.
Yes, sir.
Look after the mine for me.
And about the plan to explore the cave, don’t push it if it’s too dangerous.
Yes, Master.
Let’s go then.
Goodbye.
Bye, dear.
I’ll leave it to you, Yod.
Please let me help.
Oh, why don’t you put them in my basket? I’ll give you a lift.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
Are you Kaphrao?
Yes, how do you know my name?
The Master often mentions you to me.
I’m Wanna, his wife.
My house is over there, at the end of the farm.
Oh! You’re Miss Wanna.
That’s a lot of them.
I was going a bit too fast.
Have some fruits first.
Come.
Wow, thank you so much. They look so tasty.
So, do you need to rush back to work?
No, my boss is away today.
I can chill out all I want.
You mean Miss Fai?
Yes.
Ak told me that you and her often fight.
Is it getting better now?
I’m not sure whether it’s getting better, or because I’m getting used to it.
I feel sorry for her though.
Her mother died not even a year after giving birth to her.
Miss Panee took her in after that, so the father and daughter have become estranged.
When she grew up, Ak started to become popular with many girls lining up for him.
So, she misunderstood and always sees him as a womanizer.
And thinks her father doesn’t care about her.
When actually,
Ak loves her very dearly.
But you know, men–they just don’t know how to show it.
That’s why they end up being like this.
Oh dear, I’m talking too much.
Not at all.
Let’s just say, if there’s anything you need me to help; you can always tell me.
Thank you so much.
I’ll finish this off then.
Go ahead.
That day when Fai ditched me, she lied about having urgent matters.
She actually went out with a girl. My friend saw them at the water park.
Does she already have someone she likes?
Fai at the water park? Are you sure it’s her?
Yes, Auntie.
But dear, your friend might have mistaken it.
No, Auntie. She sent me a picture of them too.
Look.
Kaphrao!
You know her?
Who is she?
Ah! That’s why I saw Miss Fai coming back with her the other day.
And now the workers are also talking that Miss Fai often spends a lot of time with that dirty rat.
That they often go out together.
You have to do something about this, Auntie!
Geez, Miss Phrao.
It’s a day-off but you’re still working, huh?
Aren’t you going to leave it for someone else too?
Well, I have nothing to do.
It’s so boring.
Aww, is it because Miss Fai is away? You miss her, don’t you?
Nonsense!
I’m actually relieved. No one's here to keep bothering me.
Chill!
- Chill?
- Yeah.
Miss Kaphrao!
Miss Panee wants to see you now.
Right now?
Yeah.
Don't you understand the word ‘NOW’?
Fine! I’ll be right there. Right NOW!
Geez, whatever!
Holy shit!
Freaking slippery!
Hurry up! Don’t be late!
Why would Miss Panee want to see you?
I don’t trust her at all.
[Panee]: I want to see you because I need you to do something for me.
Of course, what is it?
My friend is here with her daughter.
So, I want to take them to see the cave in the mine.
I heard the workers say they've just discovered it.
You want to go to that cave?
Yes, why?
It's only been found recently. The workers barely get to explore it yet.
Maybe we should wait for the officials to explore it first.
I’m afraid it might be too dangerous.
Why would it be dangerous?
I heard Ak plans to make it a tourist attraction. I want to go there.
And you must be the one to take us there.
When do you want to go then?
Tomorrow.
But I'd need some time to prepare the place and make sure it's safe.
I’m afraid I won't be able to get everything done by–
I said tomorrow! You must do as I say.
And don't you dare make any mistake!
Auntie, I really don't get it. Why do we have to go see that stupid cave?
It’s dark and musty, and extremely hot in there.
Listen, I've done some digging up, Miss.
That Kaphrao rat is scared of the dark and narrow space.
I’ll make her hate it here and leave this place herself.
I’ll help you, Auntie.
Miss Panee wants me to take her friends to see the cave in an old mine tomorrow.
I’d like to ask for your advice on which part of the cave I could show them around.
You’re going to that cave in the mine?
Yes.
But it’s not safe to go in yet. It’ll be too dangerous.
Although the Master plans to make it a tourist attraction,
we still need the officials to approve of its safety first.
Why don’t you take them somewhere else instead?
But Miss Panee insists she wants to go there.
I guess I’ll have to do it.
Miss Panee wants Kaphrao to take her friends to see the cave?
Yes, Miss Phrao has no choice but to comply.
She doesn’t want to be in trouble so she said she’d do it.
Ak and Miss Fai are away now. What should we do?
That’s why I’m calling you, Miss Wanna.
I’d like you to help talk to Miss Panee.
She could barely stand the sight of me. I don’t know if she’ll even listen.
But I’ll give it a try.
Who allows you to enter my house?
I heard you've asked Kaphrao to take your friends to see the cave in an old mine.
It's probably too dangerous.
Why don't you go somewhere else instead? Let me–
It’s none of your concern where I’ll take my friends to.
Who are you to interfere?
I’m worried about everyone’s safety.
If you don’t mind, please let me help.
No need. You’re just a lowly mistress Ak’s been keeping at the back of the farm.
Don’t think so highly of yourself and try to mess with my business.
You’d better know your place.
Miss Panee didn’t listen to me at all. She’s so stubborn.
What should we do then?
I still can’t get a hold of Master.
There’s nothing we could do now.
Please look out for Kaphrao, Yod.
Yes, Miss.
Hey, I need to get out too.
Just a moment.
This way, please.
Do you need me to help?
I have legs, I can walk.
Hello.
This is Yod, Uncle Akanee’s assistant. He’ll help take care of us while we’re in the cave.
Hello, Miss.
Let me tell you a bit about this place.
This is a natural cave, found during the tunnel excavation.
It’s considered a medium-size cave.
From what the workers have explored so far, the inside is quite big and naturally divided into many rooms.
As for the weather inside–
Hot!
It’s so hot! And dusty too!
Look, give me some iced coffee.
I want it cold-brewed.
Coffee? We don’t have it here.
Go find it then.
My friend wants it. Don’t be rude.
For me, I’ll have premium matcha from Uji town.
With oat milk. And make sure it’s less sweet.
If you want that, it’ll take hours to get them just by car.
We can wait. Hurry up and take care of it.
Yes.
Here are your drinks.
This one is a cold-brew.
And here’s your premium matcha from Uji with oat milk and less sweet.
Thanks.
Where do you think you’re going? Unwrap the straw for me too.
Yes.
So pretty.
Now that you have your drinks, should we start moving and go inside?
Before it’d get too dark.
I’ve just sat down and barely had a sip.
Yeah, I also need 30 more minutes to do some touch-up on my makeup.
[Jirapa]: Do you think I should add more lipstick?
[Panee]: Just enjoy your mother-and-daughter time.
Here’s your torch.
A torch.
Here.
Please make sure you have your belongings with you.
There’s a stairs to go down but it’ll be quite steep.
Please don’t take pictures on your way down to prevent any accident.
That’s right. Since down there is quite dark and narrow,
I’ll be your guide from this point onwards.
Miss Kaphrao will be waiting here to coordinate with other workers for a safety purpose.
No.
Kaphrao must be the one to take us inside.
But she has never gone in there before.
I’ll feel safer if she goes with us.
That’s right.
And I’ll also have someone my age to talk to.
So?
Sure. If you’re ready, let’s go then.
Let’s go.
[Kaphrao]: Be careful.
[Panee]: I know.
Hey, not so fast.
Please be careful, the floor is quite slippery.
If anyone finds it difficult to breathe, let me know right away.
Enough with the talking. Just walk.
Yes.
Hey, why didn’t you tell me the floor is uneven there?
I’m sorry.
Seriously, you’re the worst guide ever.
This cave used to be an underground waterway.
After years of erosion, it became the walkway we’re standing on right now.
If you look at the wall carefully, you’ll see traces of flowstone or layers of sediment formed on a cave wall.
Do you see the drawing of elephants over there?
People believe it’s a baby elephant trotting after its mother.
It’s that way.
There’s nothing interesting here.
There’s probably more to see inside.
Can you take us there?
Yes.
Geez, can you go faster?
It’s bad for the elders to have their backs bent like this.
Move it.
Hey, slow down.
Can’t you see Jinda couldn’t catch up?
I’m sorry.
I just want to take you to see the interesting part as fast as I can.
But I want to spend ten more minutes here to take in the moment.
This spot is pretty too, Mum.
Let's take a picture?
Yes.
Why is it so hot outside?
Can you please hurry up a bit?
Hey, when will the van arrive? I’m dying to go home.
Please wait a moment. The driver has gone to the toilet.
Oh my goodness, why now?
Oh no, Mum!
What’s the matter, dear?
My ring! My diamond ring is gone.
Oh dear, what to do?
I’ll have someone look for it, Miss.
No! I don’t trust the workers here.
What if they keep it to themselves when they find it.
That ring is so expensive.
This is your fault. You need to go get the ring for her.
- But–
- No but!
If you can’t find it, you’re the one to be blamed. Go find it!
As for you, take me and my friends home.
I’m not going to wait for that damn van.
- Miss Phrao
- Yes?
I can ask the workers here to help look for it.
It’s okay, Uncle Yod.
Miss Panee wants to blame it on me so I must go look for it myself.
But I thought you’re afraid of the dark and narrow space.
It’s all right. There are some lights in there so it’s not that dark.
Then, please make it quick. Don’t stay there long, Miss.
Don’t worry.
You go on and drop them home.
I can get someone here to take me back.
Help…
Help me.
Please help me!
Help…
Kaphrao!
It’s me.
Fai.
Calm down. Take a deep breath.
How did you get here?
Miss Wanna couldn’t contact Dad so she called me instead.
I rushed back the minute I knew what my aunt did to you.
I’m worried about you.
I’m sorry.
It’s me who got you into this mess.
Let’s get out of here.
It was about to rain when I came in.
Or else it'll be too difficult to get out.
Mhm.
Watch your head.
Thank you.
What? A landslide at the cave?
Yes, Master. Miss Phrao and Young Master are still in the cave.
I’m waiting for the rescue team right now.
I’m on my way. Hold it down until I get there.
Holy shit! Miss Nee!
There’s a landslide at the cave! A complete chaos!
What about that girl? Did she get out of there in time?
No, no! But…
But what?
But Miss Fai also went into the cave!
How the hell did she get there?
She went to look for that girl at the mine.
When she knew that little rat was still in the cave, she went to look for her there.
It’s raining so hard the soil couldn’t hold water and collapsed.
I don’t care if you’ll dig a hole or blow it up.
You have to get my daughter and my niece out of there!
Yes, sir!
Fai! Fai!
You can’t go in there.
Let me go! I have to help my niece!
But it might collapse again.
Let me go!
Don’t just stand here. Go in there and help her!
We’re working on it, Miss.
Ak! Ak! You have to help Fai!
You have to help her!
This is all your damn fault!
They already warned you it’d be dangerous but you chose to listen to your stupid ego and forced Kaphrao to go in there!
And look what happened! Your niece has to pay for what you did! Serve you right!
Bloody hell!
I had no idea Fai would go in there!
Kaphrao.
Fai!
My dear Fai!
Get off me! Go and help them!
We’re not going to die here, are we?
Of course not.
I remember there's also another way out.
We'll definitely make it out of here, Guinea Pig.
Why didn’t you look where you’re going?
You kept swinging the torch everywhere. I couldn't see properly.
Does it hurt a lot? Can you walk?
Hop on.
What? But…
But what? Just get on my back.
If it collapses again, we'll definitely be dead.
Hold the torch for me.
Did you find it?
So?
It also got blocked.
What? So, we’re really going to die here?
We’re not gonna die here.
Trust me, everyone is doing all they can to get us out.
We just have to wait.
But you're not here alone.
I promise I'll keep you safe.
Are you cold?
Just a little.
I just don't want to see you die.
Otherwise, Dad would blame me again.
You know what, Guinea Pig?
I actually don't hate it when you're around.
I think…
I'm starting to like you now.
Kaphrao.
Kaphrao!
Phrao!
Phrao, how are you feeling?
Nod,
Why am I here?
It’s the rescue team.
They found you and Miss Fai unconscious in the cave.
What about Fai?
Is she okay?
Where is she right now?
Fai.
My dear.
Where’s Kaphrao?
She’s safe. She’s resting in the other room.
Worry about yourself first.
You almost died because of that girl.
Why did you follow her into the cave?
I already told you she’s a bloody jinx!
Panee.
You also know it’s dangerous.
Why did you tell her to go in there?
I…
I’m okay now.
I want to see Kaphrao.
Sure.
[Nod]: Drink slowly.
Thank you.
Phrao,
come work with me in Bangkok.
Can’t you see
how horrible people here treat you?
They don't like you.
I know, but I still want to be here.
Why?
Just come with me. I promise I’ll take good care of you.
I really appreciate it, Nod.
But I’ll be all right.
Can’t you hear it?
She said she wants to be here.
Guinea Pig, how are you feeling?
I’m fine.
Just leave if you’re done.
She’s in good hands now.
I’m leaving then, Phrao. I’ll drop by your place later.
How’s your ankle?
Just a bit sprained.
It’s getting much better now.
The doctor said I can go home tomorrow.
Isn't Nod your close friend? Why didn't you accept her offer and move to Bangkok to stay with her?
Well,
I…
You what?
I’m worried about Uncle.
I’m not leaving unless he wants me to.
Hey.
What?
I’m here to visit you, don’t sleep yet.
But I need to rest.
Then, get lots of rest.
I thought you said you’d rest.
How could I sleep if you keep staring?
Just close your eyes.
Why don’t you get some rest too?
But I want to stay here.
Thank you.
Now that the storm has passed.
And Miss Fai and Kaphrao are both safe.
What is it that’s still bothering your mind?
I'm worried about Kaphrao.
Well, you should be. This time, even Miss Fai almost got hurt.
I’m sure Miss Panee will not stop at this.
I think it’s time for me to do something to protect Kaphrao.
From now on, you must treat Kaphrao
as if she were my own daughter.
I want you all to look after her, and treat her just like how treat Fai.
You must always keep her safe.
Those who are rude to her, bully her, or cause her any trouble
will be considered as my enemy!
What’s going on here, Uncle?
I’m not going to let something like that cave incident happen again.
So, from now on,
you must move to live with me at the main house.
What?
Did you hear what the Master said this morning?
Why does he care about Kaphrao so much?
Or is she really his daughter?
Could be. He practically raised her up and paid for everything.
Or is she the daughter of his mistress?
Yeah, possible.
What? The workers think I’m his secret daughter?
Yes.
Last time they thought I was his kept woman.
Now, they’re saying I’m his daughter?
It’s quite possible though.
Wait!
Don’t tell me it's true?
Hey, I have a father too.
How could I be his daughter?
Aww, Miss Phrao. Please don’t be so fast to turn down a chance to become rich.
I honestly think it’s a blessing to be his daughter.
He’s rich and handsome.
And you’ll also get to have a wonderful older sister.
Look, suppose this rumour people are talking about is true,
can you give me a status as your best friend?
Nonsense, Bua! The Master only feels pity for me–that’s why he took me in.
But I don’t think he has ever felt pity for me.
It’s true that he also paid for my education.
But I never get to stay at the main house like you, Miss Phrao.
Look,
why would he be so nice to you if you’re just his worker’s kid?
Trust me, this isn’t normal. There must be more to it than you think.
I’m serious.
I already heard about the rumour.
I went to the fisherman’s wharf and people there were talking.
I really don’t know what to do…
if it turns out that I’m Uncle’s daughter.
You don’t have to do anything.
No matter whose daughter you are, you’re still you.
But even I am this confused.
I can’t imagine how Fai would feel about me.
She has to accept it and try to love you as a sister.
If this is too much for you,
why don’t you come stay with me for a while?
I’m okay. Thanks, Nod.
I always care about you.
You’re the most important person to me.
You might not know it,
but I’ve liked you for a long time since when we were in school.
But I was too afraid to let you know.
But right now, I feel that I should say it.
Because I’m scared I might lose you.
I’ll take care and watch over you.
You don’t have to answer me right now.
I just want you to give me a chance.
Please think about it.
I’m always here for you.
Hey, hey, listen.
I think…
Hello, Miss.
What is it?
I think Kaphrao is definitely the Master's secret daughter.
I knew it! That’s why Miss Panee hates her so much.
That's it.
She’s probably afraid that girl will steal everything from Young Master.
I also heard that the Master was quite a player back then.
Really?
Yes, so many girls to warm his bed–old and young.
Mhm.
Come to think of it, there used to be a rumour that he liked to flirt around.
Yeah, I guess it's all true.
Kaphrao is definitely the Master's secret daughter.
She’s afraid that girl will steal everything from Young Master.
[Akanee]: Kaphrao will live with us. From now on, she’s your sister.
You must look after her.
Why do you always pick on her?
[Panee]: What if she’s the kid of your father’s mistress?
[Akanee]: Kaphrao has graduated. I want her to help me with my work here.
You should take her with you to Nam’s grand opening.
Show her around
and introduce her to your siblings.
Are we really sisters?
There’s a rumour spreading among the workers that Kaphrao is your daughter.
Last time, they said she was my kept woman.
And now, she’s my daughter?
But I can see why they think that.
I’m deeply indebted to Kaphrao’s father.
Hey, don’t tell me you also believe this rumour.
That’s not funny.
What if Miss Panee hears about it? Kaphrao would surely be in trouble.
You’re right.
Aww, Miss Phrao, you’re so diligent.
Just as I thought!
You’re a complete wreck to Fai’s life.
You’re stealing everything from her!
That cave incident, Fai almost couldn’t get out of there alive.
All because of you, you damn jinx!
You made her lie to me and put her in danger.
Get the hell out of Akanee Group!
Get out of her life right now!
Aunt Nee, that’s enough!
Stop talking to her like that!
You still try to defend her?
She’s going to steal everything from you!
She almost got you killed!
Kaphrao is under my care.
Just blame it on me.
How can you say that?
Enough, Panee!
Ak.
Look at her. Your daughter is trying to protect your mistress’s kid.
Kaphrao isn’t my mistress’s kid.
And you don’t have the right to talk to her like that!
Then what is she?
Why the hell would you tell her to move into the main house?
She’s the daughter of someone I’m indebted to.
Her father saved my life.
[Akanee]: I’m not afraid.
I’ve won this auction for mining lease legally.
I don’t care if anyone doesn’t want to play by the rules.
[Arthit]: Look out, Master!
Let’s go!
This way!
Arthit!
Master, look out!
Are you all right, Master?
Please look after my daughter.
Arthit.
Arthit!
Her father saved my life so many times
from those powerful thugs whom I got in their way.
But in the end,
her father died because of me.
He sacrificed his life for me.
Liar!
I don’t believe you!
You made that up just to protect this girl!
Do you really want me to believe that a stupid worker like that would sacrifice his life for you?
Liar!
Watch it, Panee! You should have some respect for others!
I order everyone here to never talk about this again!
You’re a nasty bitch!
A good-for-nothing! You're ruining Fai’s life!
Aunt Nee!
- Yod!
- Please stop!
Stop!
- Miss Panee!
- Aunt Nee!
Please stop it! Stop!
You nasty bitch!
Please don’t!
Get off me!
You scumbag! Get back here!
How is Kaphrao?
She still hasn’t said anything.
So, where are you taking her?
Maybe somewhere to get our heads straight first.
I don’t want her to see Aunt Nee.
Good, better wait for it to die down before coming back.
Look after her for me.
I will.
Drink something first.
I’ve always believed my dad died in an accident.
Now, I know…why Uncle is so nice to me.
Are you mad at my dad?
No, I don’t blame him.
And I’m proud of what my dad did.
I’m sorry.
Your dad did all he could to protect my dad.
But I still let Aunt Nee hurt you. I couldn’t protect you at all.
You did protect me today.
Thank you.
So, where are we going?
Somewhere to take refuge—away from all this madness.
We’ll come back when things get better.
[Next Episode]
Please don’t go see that nasty girl again, dear.
You also hate her to your guts, don’t you?
And I hate you so much too!
Phrao!
Give her some time.
She’ll come out when she feels better.
Hurry up and say it.
I actually don’t hate you.
Then, how do you feel about me?
I…
Forget it. I don’t want to know anymore.
Kaphrao! Hold on!
If I were kind like you, calm like Nam, and sweet like Lom–
she might have liked me more.
I’m sure she’ll like you the way you are.
♫I still remember vividly that day when we first met♫
♫Those memories we had together never fade away from my heart♫
♫We might never say it out loud how we feel for each other♫
♫But deep down we both know how we feel♫
♫Those things in the past, I still can’t forget them♫
♫I want to know if you’re like that too–do you also feel the same?♫
♫I could never forget those eyes of yours♫
♫The warmth you used to give me, I still remember it vividly♫
♫No matter for how long, you’ll always remain in my heart♫
♫All those years I’ve been waiting, for us to finally be together again♫
[North Star Entertainment]
[Flaming Chains of Love]